{
    "id": "ed44b5b5858a4944ac8937a27eb9f368",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Put a small quantity of sugar ………………… the batter.",
            "description": "Into is common after put to talk about directional movement. ",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "onto",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My quarrel is ……………………. the under-representation of women here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A quarter of the population voted …………………… him.",
            "description": "You vote for or against somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The restaurant offered us a quasi hamburger made ……………………. vegetables.",
            "description": "Made is used with of when we identify the material used to make something.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Direct all queries ……………………… your nearest dealer.",
            "description": "To indicates direction. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The police queried him ……………………….. his whereabouts the night of the crime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Iced tea will quench your thirst ……………………… hot days.",
            "description": "We use on with days.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The salesman pushed the product ………………………… every opportunity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The people shivered ………………………. fear when their village was invaded.",
            "description": "With is used in a number of expressions like shiver with, tremble with etc.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a quality of kindness that appeals ……………………………. everyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Only applicants ………………………… the proper qualifications will be considered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He had no qualms ………………………… robbing the poor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}